There are several reasons why relational databases are like this.
هناك أسباب عدة تجعل قواعد البيانات الارتباطية تبدو هكذا.
Let's focus on two of the most important ones.
فلنركِّز على اثنين من أهم هذه الأسباب.
First, orders and accounts are different types
أولًا؛ الطلبات والحسابات نوعان مختلفان
of objects and will be easier to organize if kept separate.
من الكائنات، وسيكون ترتيبهما أسهل إذا تم الإبقاء عليهما منفصلين.
Second, this multi-table structure allows queries to execute more quickly.
ثانيًا؛ هذا البناء متعدد الجداول يسمح للاستعلامات بالتنفيذ بشكل أسرع.
Let's look at each of these points more closely.
فلنلقِ نظرة أكثر قربًا على كلٍ من هذه النقاط.
The account and orders tables store fundamentally different types of objects.
تخزن جداول الحسابات والطلبات نوعين مختلفين من الكائنات بالأساس.
Parch and Posey probably only wants one account per company,
ربما لا يرغب بارش وبوسي سوى في حساب واحد لكل شركة،
and they wanted to be up-to-date with the latest information.
وأرادا أن يتلقيا تحديثات بآخر المعلومات.
Orders, on the other hand,
على الجانب الآخر، يُرجح
are likely to stay the same once they are entered,
أن تظل الطلبات كما هي بمجرد إدخالها،
and certainly, once they're filled.
وبمجرد ملئها بالتأكيد.
A given customer might have multiple orders,
ربما توجد عدة طلبات لدى عميل ما،
and rather than change a past order,
وبدلًا من تغيير طلب سابق
Parch and Posey might just add a new one.
قد يضيف بارش وبوسي طلبًا جديدًا فحسب.
Because these objects operate differently,
ولأن هذه الكائنات تعمل بشكل متباين،
it makes sense for them to live in different tables.
فمن المنطقي أن توجد في جداول مختلفة.
Another reason accounts and orders might be stored
هناك سبب آخر يفرض على الحسابات والطلبات التي ربما تم تخزينها
separately has to do with the speed at which databases can modify data.
بشكل منفصل أن تدير الأمر في حدود السرعة التي يمكن لقواعد البيانات تعديل البيانات عندها.
When you write a query, its execution speed
حين تكتبون استعلامًا فإن سرعة تنفيذه
depends on the amount of data you're asking the database to
تعتمد على كمّ البيانات الذي تطلبون من قاعدة البيانات
read and the number and type of calculations you're asking it to make.
قراءته، ورقم ونوع الحسابات التي تطلبون منها أن تجريها.
Imagine a world where the account names and addresses are added into the orders table.
تخيَّلوا عالمًا تتم فيه إضافة أسماء وعناوين الحسابات إلى جدول الطلبات.
This means, the table would have six additional columns: one for account name,
هذا يعني أن الجدول سيتضمن ست أعمدة إضافية: واحد منها لاسم الحساب
and five that make up the street address,
وخمسة أعمدة تعوِّض عن عنوان الشارع
city, state, zip code, and country.
والمدينة والولاية والرمز البريدي والدولة.
Let's say, a customer changes their address.
لنقُل إن عميلًا يغير عنوانه.
In this world, the five address columns
في هذا العالم، تحتاج أعمدة العناوين الخمسة
need to be updated retroactively for every single order.
إلى التحديث بأثر رجعي عند كل طلب،
This means five updates times the number of orders that they've made.
وهذا يعني خمس تحديثات بعدد الطلبات التي أجراها العميل.
By contrast, keeping account details in
على النقيض من ذلك، فإن حفظ تفاصيل الحساب
a separate table makes this only a total of five updates.
في جدول منفصل يجعل هذا ما مجموعه خمس تحديثات فحسب.
The larger the data set, the more that this matters.
كلما كانت مجموعة البيانات أكبر حدث ذلك بمعدل أكبر.
There are more reasons for this kind of structure but for now,
هناك مزيد من الأسباب لهذا النوع من البناء، لكن حتى الآن
what you really need to know is how to connect the account data and order data.
فإن ما تحتاجون معرفته حقًا هو كيفية توصيل بيانات الحساب ببيانات الطلب.
The mechanism for doing that is a JOIN, which you'll learn next.
الآلية لفعل ذلك هي رابط؛ وهو ما ستتعلمونه فيما يلي.